(Penny:)She's adorable, Howard.
I think you'll like her.
(Penny:)Great.
(Howard:)What did you tell her about me?
Did you mention body fat?
(Penny:)No, I thought
that'd be a nice surprise for her.
(Howard:)Good, good.
I told her you're an aerospace engineer,
you speak five languages--
(Howard:)Six, if you count Klingon.
(Leonard:)Girls don't count Klingon, Howard.
(Leonard:)-Right?
-Right.
(Penny:)And I told her you have
an unhealthy attachment to your mother.
(Leonard:)-What?
-I'm kidding.
(Leonard:)Another delightful surprise for her.
(Raj:)Sheldon, it's your play.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)My Enchanted Troll bludgeons
your Screaming Harpy...
(Sheldon:)...with a Cursed Mace. Game.
(Raj:)Sorry, boys. Say hi to your mother
when she picks you up.
(Raj:)Or I could just tell her later tonight.
Ha-ha-ha.